<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Renga Theme for Hugo on Jordan Hutchings</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Renga Theme for Hugo on Jordan Hutchings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Plotting dynamic maps with mapview</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-08-10-plotting-dynamic-maps-with-mapview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-08-10-plotting-dynamic-maps-with-mapview/</guid>
      <description>I’ve spent a lot of time working with spatial data recently, and came across a cool tool to display maps that I thought was worth writing about. Here are some of the cool features you can find in mapview.
I’ll be using the included breweries, and franconia datasets to show off some of the features I found useful for making dynamic maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webscraping Craigslist Apartments Listings with R</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-07-15-webscraping-craigslist-apartments-listings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-07-15-webscraping-craigslist-apartments-listings/</guid>
      <description>While looking for an apartment to rent in Toronto, I found myself checking Craigslist multiple times throughout the day for new postings. The recent rising interest rates have led to an increased demand for rental units in Toronto, and consequently made the rental market much more competitive and difficult to maneuver. This post describes the craigslist web crawler bot I created in order to identify new relevant apartment listings, and have the results sent to your phone as push notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masters Fantasy Golf Tournament Dashboard</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-06-12-masters-fantasy-golf-tournament-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-06-12-masters-fantasy-golf-tournament-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>This blog posts shows how I use the cronR package to automate a fantasy golf pool with some friends for the golf major tournaments.
The process takes four steps:
Collect the leader board data Prepare the data Publish the data to GoogleSheets Automate the script with cronR  Lets use the 2022 Masters tournament as an example of how we set up the pipeline.
Collecting Leaderboard Data I’ve found success using two different methods here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Fantasy Losers Pool</title>
      <link>/blog/2021-11-19-nfl-fantasy-losers-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021-11-19-nfl-fantasy-losers-pool/</guid>
      <description>The 2021 NFL Losers Pool I’ve entered into an annual NFL Losers Pool with some friends. A Losers Pool is a fantasy NFL league where each competitor in the league is required to pick any team playing that week to lose their game. If the picked team wins, the player is eliminated from the pool. The players who correctly picked a losing team that week move on and must pick a new team to lose the following week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscanious Information</title>
      <link>/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/misc/</guid>
      <description>Here is a catch all for useful links and resources I come across.
Useful Links  R Styler: a package to style your code. R for Data Science: A free online textbook written by Hadley Wickham and Garrett Grolemund. Mastering R Shiny: A free online guide to developing Shiny apps. One Year to Dissertate: Writing your dissertation in RStudio. Yihui Xie | One Markdown Document, Fourteen Demos: Showing off some of the capabilities available in R Markdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Working papers and work in progress  The Impact of Easing Stay at Home Orders on US Businesses  Working draft Master’s Summer Paper How the implementation and removal of Stay at Home orders during the COVID-19 pandemic shaped mobility and spending patterns in the US.  Does Yelp Impact where we choose to eat?  Working draft \(\cdot\) Poster Undergraduate Thesis Do recent Yelp ratings influence the number of people who visit a restaurant?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
