<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>R on Jordan Hutchings</title>
    <link>/tags/r/</link>
    <description>Recent content in R on Jordan Hutchings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/r/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Plotting dynamic maps with mapview</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-08-10-plotting-dynamic-maps-with-mapview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-08-10-plotting-dynamic-maps-with-mapview/</guid>
      <description>I’ve spent a lot of time working with spatial data recently, and came across a cool tool to display maps that I thought was worth writing about. Here are some of the cool features you can find in mapview.
I’ll be using the included breweries, and franconia datasets to show off some of the features I found useful for making dynamic maps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webscraping Craigslist Apartments Listings with R</title>
      <link>/blog/2022-07-15-webscraping-craigslist-apartments-listings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2022-07-15-webscraping-craigslist-apartments-listings/</guid>
      <description>While looking for an apartment to rent in Toronto, I found myself checking Craigslist multiple times throughout the day for new postings. The recent rising interest rates have led to an increased demand for rental units in Toronto, and consequently made the rental market much more competitive and difficult to maneuver. This post describes the craigslist web crawler bot I created in order to identify new relevant apartment listings, and have the results sent to your phone as push notifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFL Fantasy Losers Pool</title>
      <link>/blog/2021-11-19-nfl-fantasy-losers-pool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2021-11-19-nfl-fantasy-losers-pool/</guid>
      <description>The 2021 NFL Losers Pool I’ve entered into an annual NFL Losers Pool with some friends. A Losers Pool is a fantasy NFL league where each competitor in the league is required to pick any team playing that week to lose their game. If the picked team wins, the player is eliminated from the pool. The players who correctly picked a losing team that week move on and must pick a new team to lose the following week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
